silverbearcafe.com 2005-03-05

# The Silver Bear Cafe Privacy Statement

**The Silver Bear Cafe** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [silverbearcafe.com](http://www.silverbearcafe.com/)

###  Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. This information is also used to allow us to determine statistical usage of the website and rings. 

The refering URL (the webpage you left before coming to a Silver Bear Cafe webpage, if any) is logged whenever you view a page on the Silver Bear Cafe website. This allows us to see which areas are more popular than others on the website, the paths taken to reach each page, and it also allows us to gauge the effectiveness of any promotional programs we may be running at the time. 

All such information is gathered globally rather than individually, and no information is linked to any identifying information about you. Such aggregated data may be disclosed, for example, to potential and current advertisers providing them with information about the number of people viewing their ads and how many have clicked on them. 

###  Personal Information 

No personal information is collected by The Silver Bear Cafe from visitors to the our website, when viewing pages, or when navigating password protected area. We also do not collect or harvest the EMail addresses of people who EMail us directly. We only use them to respond to your queries. 

When joining The Silver Bear Cafe, the personal information provided will be made available to the fufillment department for the sole purpose of managing their reward compensation and emailing members with Silver Bear Cafe related information only. 

Except as provided for above, Any personal information collected will not be disclosed to any third party. 

###  Children's Guidelines 

Currently this site has no visible links that are unsuitable for children. 

We also require personal information, in the form of a Name and EMail address in order to obtain our members services. For these reasons, children age 13 and under are not knowingly allowed to become members of the The Silver Bear Cafe website, and thus create or join a Net Ring provided by our service.
